thetruckersreport.com 2011-06-18

# Privacy Policy | TruckersReport.com

**Privacy Policy for www.thetruckersreport.com**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at admin@truckersreport.com.

At www.thetruckersreport.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.thetruckersreport.com and how it is used.

All automated email from TheTruckersReport.com comes with instructions on how to unsubscribe from our mailing list.  If you wish to unsubscribe but are not able to follow the instructions, please email your unsubscribe request to admin@truckersreport.com and your email address will be manually removed.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.thetruckersreport.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.thetruckersreport.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.thetruckersreport.com.

  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include …….  
Google Adsense

Commission Junction

Adbrite

Chitika

Amazon

Vibrant Media

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.thetruckersreport.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.thetruckersreport.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.thetruckersreport.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

We can be reached via e-mail at [admin@thetruckersreport.com](mailto:admin@thetruckersreport.com)

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes the visitor’s IP address.

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who post messages to our bulletin board, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, the e-mail addresses of those who make postings to our chat areas, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, internal marketing purposes, and disclosed when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Website and applicable laws or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Website.

We reserve the right to publicly expose IP addresses or email addresses which might identify employers or even individual computer owners if there is abuse or attempts to misrepresent their relationship to an employer or business (Shilling, astro-turfing, sock puppetry).

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to store visitors preferences, ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads.

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by e-mailing us at the above address.

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to a description of information that we maintain about them.

Consumers can access this information by e-mail us at the above address.

With respect to security: When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial or health information, we redirect visitors to a secure server and will notify visitors through a pop-up screen on our site.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number.
